pakistanidramaz.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Pakistani Dramas

**Privacy Policy**

****Pakistanidramaz.com care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy. By registering to Pakistanidramaz.com you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.

We use cookies with minimal information in them.  
We use Google Analytics, which is covered by Google’s Privacy policy  
We allow you to contact other members via profile pages, but no private information is sent unless you want them to see.  
If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.  
In details What does Pakistanidramaz.com Privacy Policy Covers?  
All the personal information we collect is noted on your profile page. That includes your name, email, date of birth and biographic information. The personal information that you provide is used for Registration purpose. In order for you to participate in Pakistanidramaz.com discussion you must complete a registration form. As part of registration form, we require your email address.

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Adsense, extendmedia, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.  
Profile Information  
Pakistanidramaz.com allow other users to browse your full name, instant messaging URL, and other details within your member profile should you provide this optional information. Pakistanidramaz.com allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**What about Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser in order to check in if you are logged in or out. All the other information is located in Pakistanidramaz.com server. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Membership Validity?**

We reserve the right to delete any message, ban any member for any or no reason whatsoever. Members found to be abusing the contact form, using it for commercial purposes, or otherwise breaking the Community Guidelines will have his/her membership suspended. Please read Disclaimer for more information.

**Children below 13 DO NOT Register**

The Federal Trade Commission’s Children Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) require that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you cannot use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.
